RG 073, Department of Veterans' Affairs
Connecticut State Library
- Series 6. Miscellaneous Records, 1878-1951; 1992-031
  - Benjamin Fitch letter to the Trustees, 1865 October 3; original + typed copy on foam board. (Box Item 14)
    Letter taken from cornerstone of the administrative building at Fitch's Home on February 11, 1937.
    Restored in 1989